

Personal info

+962785584039 Sarah.abed.elrazeq@gmail.com Amman, Jordan Linked in Portfolio GitHub **Codeforces**

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Skills

Hackerrank

Frameworks/ Libraries: React is, Next is, TypeScript, React ts, Bootstrap, SASS

Tools: Redux, SEO, Git, Github

Personal:

Problem-Solving, Graphic design, and drawing, Marketing, Teamwork Skills, UX, UI design,

Languages

Arabic & English

Sarah Abed El Razeq

Software Engineer

Overflow

I am a self-motivated software engineer specializing in front-end development with demonstrated experience in JavaScript and web interface development. A problem solver with a zest for solving complex issues Unstoppable in learning new technologies and integrating them.

Experience

Merwas, Queen Rania st. — Front-End Engineer

Feb 2022 - Feb 2023

- Shipped quality code aggressively to ensure projects were finished on time with minimal bugs
- Frameworks/ Libraries: React Js Bootstrap Redux Next Js

Future Auric For Business Solutions, Al Jandawil — Front-End Engineer

Feb 2021 - January 2022

Own business, Online/social media — Handmade, seller, manager September 2018 - March 2020

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Sciences

2021

Al-al Bayt University

Awards

AFRICA & ARAB Collegiate Programming Championship

December 2020 Twelfth Place